Guide to the Sara and Gerald Murphy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1911-1980; Series I; 3.75 linear feet (9 boxes)
  - Lowndes, Marion "Diddy" and Lloyd, 1940-1967, undated (Box 5, Folder 91-94)
  - L______, A. B., 1947 June (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - "M" general, 1963 September 12, undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - MacLeish, Ada, 1935-1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 97-99)
    Includes letters from other MacLeish family members.
  - MacLeish, Ada, 1935-1969, undated (Box 6, Folder 100-102)
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1928-1964, undated (Box 6, Folder 103)
    Includes copy of MacLeish's sermon on The Book of Job delivered at the First Church of Christ in Farmington, Connecticut (1955), inscribed by MacLeish.
  - Maxwell, William, 1911-1962, undated (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - McLaughlin, Harrison L., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Mermet, Helene, 1946-1963 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Metz, Clara, 1937, 1940, undated (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Meyer, Marcelle, no year, August 19 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Milford, Nancy, 1965 July (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Mitchell, Sara, 1935-1965, undated (Box 6, Folder 110-111)
  - Mizener, Arthur, 1948-1957 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Montgomery, Buffie, 1951, 1958, undated (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Morgan, Theresa, 1951-1961 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Murphy, Baoth, 1934 December 4, undated (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Murphy, Gerald, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    Contains postcard and several gift cards sent from Gerald Murphy to Sara Murphy
  - Murphy, Gerald, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Murphy, Patrick, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - "N" general, 1948 February 18, undated (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - National Broadcasting Corporation, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Nicholas, Archbishop of Serbia, 1937-1941 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Nyberg, Lillie M., 1934-1953 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Ober, Harold, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - O'Hara, John, 1962 July 30 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Orloff, Vladimir, 1934-1964, undated (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - "P" general, 1919 January 3 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Pagano, Mark, 1964, undated (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Parker, Dorothy and Alan Campbell, 1929-1964, undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
    Includes photocopies of letters from Parker to third parties dated 1929-1930.
  - Perkins, Maxwell E. (Maxwell Evarts), 1941-1945 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Peto, Ruby, 1939-1950, undated (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Peters, Rollo, 1964 September 10, undated (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Pfeifer, Jinny, 1935-1957, undated (Box 7, Folder 132-133)
  - Pfeiffer, Pauline
    Related Archival Materials note
    See: Box 4, folders 72-73, Hemingway, Pauline
  - Pickman, Hester and Betsy, 1935-1966, undated (Box 7, Folder 134-135)
  - Porter, Cole, 1942-1965, undated (Box 8, Folder 136-137)
    Includes "Cole Porter: Some Unpublished Lyrics."
  - Porter, Jeffrey, undated (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Powell, Dawn, 1942-1964, undated (Box 8, Folder 139-142)
  - Purdy, Ken and Lucille, 1944-1951 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Quintanilla, Luis, 1940 December 18 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - "R" general, 1918-1963 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Rogers, Herman, 1937, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Roussel, Yvonne, 1935, 1937, undated (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Rutland, Violet, Dowager Duchess of, 1937 July 21 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Ryan, Edward S., 1952 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - "S" general, 1918-1957 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Seldes, Gilbert, 1957, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Sella, André, Hotel du Cap d'Antibes, 1959 August 30, undated (Box 9, Folder 152)
    Includes postcard of Hotel du Cap d'Antibes
  - Smith, Scottie Fitzgerald, 1941-1945, undated (Box 9, Folder 153)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1952 December 11 (Box 9, Folder 154)
  - Stewart, Donald Ogden, undated (Box 9, Folder 155)
  - Stewart, Helen, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 156)
  - "T" general, 1956 December 23 (Box 9, Folder 157)
  - Tolstoy, Beatrice, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Tolstoy, Ilya A., 1940-1965 (Box 9, Folder 159)
  - Tripet-Skrypitzine, Oleg and Minda, 1949-1966, undated (Box 9, Folder 160)
  - Trudeau, Helen and Francis, 1937-1964 (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - Turnbull, Andrew W., 1957-1980 (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - United Air Lines, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - "V" general, 1919-1964 (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Vom Rath, Cecilia, 1935, 1963, undated (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - "W" general, 1919-1958 (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - Walker, Hale, 1936-1953 (Box 9, Folder 167-168)
  - Whitney, John Hay, 1942-1953, undated (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Wilson, Edmund, 1942 June, undated (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Woollcott, Alexander, 1935-1945 (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Woolley, Monty, 1911-1963, undated (Box 9, Folder 172-173)
  - Yarmolinsky, Harriet, 1962, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - Unidentified correspondents, 1937-1965, undated (Box 9, Folder 175)
- Personal Papers, 1884-1962; Series II; 4.17 linear feet (11 boxes)
  The series is organized into four subseries: Diaries and Notebooks, Scrapbooks, Other Papers, and Printed Materials.
  The series contains material pertaining to the Murphy family's personal lives. Most notably, diaries, notebooks, and other documents, such as recipes, address books, and printed material, provide an intimate glimpse into the Murphy family's daily life. The series also includes material belonging to their sons Patrick and Baoth Murphy.
  Gerald Murphy's diaries date to his life as a student at Phillips Academy in Andover, Massachusetts, and to his early years of fatherhood. Sara Murphy's diaries, while not continuous, date from 1896 to the 1940s. Her diaries represent particularly rich documentation of her interior life while an adolescent and young adult. Sara Murphy's childhood is also represented in her scrapbook of greeting cards, which dates from 1895 to 1897. The early years of the Murphys' marriage, and the birth of their daughter, are traced in Sara's diary from 1917-1918.
  The Other Papers subseries contains a range of documents that chronicle the Murphys' lifestyle and friendships. For example, address books, calling cards, and business cards provide insight into the Murphys' various contacts and everyday life, particularly while they were living in France. The Murphys' recipes for cocktails and food are also found here and are suggestive of their reputation as artful hosts. Many of the recipes are annotated with notes about friends' contributions or culinary tastes. There are also a number of drawings by the Murphy children. Gerald Murphy's notes on landscape architecture, some housed in their original box, are also present and date from his period as a student at Harvard University.
  Scrapbooks and printed materials illustrate the Murphys' pursuits and those of their children. For example, the paper "Auto-Gammier" roulette bought in France indicates the Murphys' musical interests. Among the printed materials are two pieces by Archibald MacLeish, Frescoes for Mr. Rockefeller's City and "Lettre d'Amérique Pour Gérard Murphy," given to the Murphys by MacLeish. The maps, brochures, and other travel information attest to the Murphy family's frequent relocation, and Sara Murphy's scrapbook of postcards indicates her early traveling experience. Patrick Murphy's collection of publications on hunting and fishing and Baoth Murphy's Bible with gun drawings and school publications are a window into their boyhoods. Similarly, Patrick Murphy's diaries, alphabetized "to do" list, and other notebooks represent his childhood and struggle with tuberculosis.
  - Diaries and Notebooks
    - Gerald Murphy
      - "Gerald C. Murphy, Andover" notebook containing various words and their definitions, 1907-1908 (Box 10, Folder 176)
      - Notebook with various addresses and a list of names considered for Baoth Murphy, circa 1919 (Box 10, Folder 177)
    - Sara Murphy
      - Diary, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 178)
      - Diary, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 179)
      - Diary, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 180)
      - Diary, 1910-1915 (Box 10, Folder 181)
      - Diary, 1917-1918 (Box 10, Folder 182)
      - Diary, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 183)
      - Diary, 1940-1942 (Box 11, Folder 184)
    - Patrick Murphy
      - "Fishing Record" notebook containing angling license and notes about fishing at Penlake, Ontario, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 185)
      - "Hunting Record" notebook, empty, circa 1933 (Box 11, Folder 186)
      - Notebook with essays on "Columbus" and "Leap Year" and list of addresses, circa 1934 (Box 11, Folder 187)
      - Notebook with essays and notes on Latin, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 188)
      - Small telephone book containing alphabetized "to do" list, circa 1935 (Box 11, Folder 189)
      - Diary, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 190)
      - Diary, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 191)
      - "Chemcraft Chemistry Outfit Note Book", undated (Box 12, Folder 192)
      - Brown leather scrapbook with clippings on boats, tanning, taxidermy, making camping equipment and other activities, 1936
        "Patrick Murphy" carved on inside cover
  - Scrapbooks
    - Scrapbook with greeting cards, 1895-1897
    - Scrapbook with postcards of Europe, 1905
    - "A Debutante Book" (empty), circa 1907
    - Scrapbook with newspaper clippings on WWII, 1940s
  - Other Papers
    - "The Bride Elect" guest book from the Murphys' wedding, 1915 (Box 12, Folder 193)
    - Certificate appointing Gerald Murphy Second Lieutenant in the Aviation Section of the Signal Officers' Reserve Corps of the Army of the United States, 1918 April 8
    - Birth certificate for Baoth Murphy, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 194)
    - Gerald Murphy's notes on gardening and architecture, circa 1919 (Box 12, Folder 195)
    - Gerald Murphy's notes on landscape architecture (written on index cards) and original metal box in which cards were stored, circa 1919 (Box 20)
    - Gerald Murphy's notes on Italian language, circa 1938 (Box 12, Folder 196)
    - Gerald Murphy's collection of notes, clippings, and other ephemera and wooden box in which they were formerly stored, 1940-1962, undated (Box 13, Folder 197-201)
    - List of Murphys' homes, undated (Box 13, Folder 202)
    - Address books, circa 1915-1930s (Box 13, Folder 203)
      Includes loose addresses removed from leather file folder (such as a slip of paper with Picasso's address)
      Includes address books made by Mark Cross
    - Address books, circa 1915-1930s (Box 14, Folder 204-209)
    - Business cards, calling cards, and addresses, undated (Box 14, Folder 210)
      Includes calling card for "Mme. & Mr. Camille Bombois, artiste peintre, Pavilion des Roses, Rue de Montbuisson, tele: bougival 381, Bougival (S. & O.)" with Matisse's name and address on the back
    - Survey of Villa America property by G. Vailland, 1932 June
    - Guest book for Murphys' home "Swan Cove", 1946 (Box 15, Folder 211)
    - Assorted recipes and menus (including food sayings from Gerald), 1954, undated (Box 15, Folder 212-214)
    - Collection of recipes "For Honoria", 1950 October (Box 15, Folder 215)
    - "Dinner for Ulric Bell" menu, 1942 January 5 (Box 15, Folder 216)
    - "Everything I Love Let's Face It" by Cole Porter and "You're on My Mind" by Kalmor and Ruby musical scores transcribed by Patrick Murphy, undated (Box 15, Folder 217-218)
    - Photocopy of Gerald Murphy's list of California businesses, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 219)
    - Photograph of membership certificate for the "Weather Bird" in the "Yacht Club de France" and fabric samples, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 220)
    - Christmas cards (including card painted by Baoth Murphy), undated (Box 15, Folder 221)
    - Samples of Chinese tea chest papers from the Stevens-Nelson Paper Corporation, undated (Box 15, Folder 222)
    - Patrick Murphy's membership card in The National Association of Audubon Societies and Christmas card from Sidney W. Fish, 1936-1937 (Box 15, Folder 223)
    - Drawings by Baoth Murphy, Before 1936 (Box 15, Folder 224)
    - Duotang with artwork by Patrick Murphy, 1936 Summer (Box 15, Folder 225)
    - Spiral-bound notebook with artwork by Patrick Murphy, Before 1937 (Box 15, Folder 226)
    - Loose drawings and paintings by Patrick Murphy, Before 1937 (Box 16, Folder 227)
    - Etching of Ernest Hemingway by Patrick Murphy, Before 1937 (Box 16, Folder 228)
    - Drawings by Robert Benchley's son, undated (Box 16, Folder 229)
    - Unsigned children's drawings and empty portfolio case, undated
    - Case for traveler's cheques, undated (Box 16, Folder 230)
    - Brown file folder with initials "H.M.", undated (Box 16, Folder 231)
    - List of artists studied, 1936-1937 (Box 16, Folder 232)
    - Personalized notepads belonging to Gerald Murphy, undated (Box 16, Folder 233-235)
    - Small black notebook (empty), undated (Box 16, Folder 236)
    - Looseleaf memo booksheets (empty), undated (Box 16, Folder 237)
    - Luggage tag for Baoth Murphy, circa 1934 (Box 16, Folder 238)
    - "Specifications for the House of Mr. and Mrs. Gerald Murphy, Sneden's Landing", circa 1949 (Box 16, Folder 239)
    - Blueprints and plans for renovations to "Cheer Hall," Sneden's Landing, by Hale Walker, circa 1949
    - Diploma for Gerald Murphy from Saint Joseph's Abbey, 1964 October 20
    - Gerald Murphy's will, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 240)
    - Copy of Sara Murphy's death certificate, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 241)
    - Empty quatrefoil folder, undated
  - Printed Materials
    - William Tonks & Sons "Book of Furnishing Brassfoundry and Patented Articles", 1884 (Box 17, Folder 242)
    - Harper's Weekly with articles on "China To-Day," "Opening of the Season at the Larchmont Yacht Club, New York," and "The Gray Man" by S.R. Crockett, circa 1895 (Box 17, Folder 243)
    - "Grüsse von Nah und Fern" postcard album, 1898-1899 (Box 17, Folder 244)
    - Program for "A Tribute to Maréchal Joffre from The Citizens of New York", 1917 May 10 (Box 17, Folder 245)
    - Clipping of The New York Times with photograph of Baoth Murphy, 1926 November 7 (Box 17, Folder 246)
    - Paper "Auto-Gammier" roulette representing musical scales, keys, solfège, and corresponding accidentals, and cover bought from Au Virtuose, undated (Box 17, Folder 247)
    - Franciscan prayer cards, undated (Box 17, Folder 248)
    - The New England Quarterly, 1932 April (Box 17, Folder 249)
    - Frescoes for Mr. Rockefeller's City by Archibald MacLeish (New York: The John Day Company), 1933 (Box 17, Folder 250)
    - Allerlei: Introducing 500 Common Words and 30 Idioms by Peter Hagboldt belonging to Baoth Murphy, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 251)
    - Bible with gun drawings belonging to Baoth Murphy, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 252)
    - The Harvey Rambler with story "Ghost, or No Ghost?" (Volume 10, No. 2) and poem "Ppooeemm" (Volume 10, No. 3) by Baoth Murphy, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 253)
    - The Dragon by Saint George's School (Newport, R.I.), Volume 37, Number 2, 1934 December 18 (Box 17, Folder 254)
    - "Lettre d'Amérique Pour Gérard Murphy" by Archibald MacLeish in Mesures, 1935 April 15 (Box 17, Folder 255)
    - Saint George's Calendar, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 256)
    - Miniature calendars for 1935 and 1937 (Box 17, Folder 257)
    - Advertisements from The Literary Digest and Ladies Home Journal, 1918 and 1927
    - "Points of Interest At Colorado Springs", undated (Box 17, Folder 258)
    - "Liberty map of the Western Front, Together with a Complete Area Map of the Great World War Showing the Battle-Line of Liberty, also the Lines of the Farthest Invasions of German and Allied Territory" by The Literary Digest, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 259)
    - Bacon's Motoring Map of England & Wales, South Sheet. (Large Print Motoring Map of the Arterial Roads and By-Passes around London), 1927 (Box 18, Folder 260)
    - Maps of France, 1930s (Box 18, Folder 261-263)
    - Map of Canadian National Railways, undated (Box 18, Folder 264)
    - Road Map from Lake Ontario to Huntsville and Lake of Bays, circa 1934 (Box 18, Folder 265)
    - Map of Saranac Lake, New York, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 266)
    - "Adirondack Canoe Routes" and map, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 267)
    - "Adirondack Campsites" and map, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 268)
    - Map of New York State, circa 1930 (Box 18, Folder 269)
    - Map of Randall's Island Park, New York, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 270)
    - Map of St. Regis Yacht Club, undated (Box 18, Folder 271)
    - "Flies and Fly Tackle by Weber" catalogue, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 272)
    - Pflueger Fishing Tackle catalogues, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 273-274)
    - Applications for stocking fish in public waters, partially completed by Patrick Murphy, for State of New York, circa 1933 (Box 19, Folder 275)
    - Leather Craft by M. Parisi, circa 1930 (Box 19, Folder 276)
    - "What To Do With Minerals" by C.E. Cole, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 277)
    - "Fall Plantings to Attract Wild Ducks, Fish, Furs, and Folks", 1928 (Box 19, Folder 278)
    - "Propagation of Upland Game Birds," U.S. Department of Agriculture Farm Bulletin No. 1613, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 279)
    - Farm Animals by James Gilchrist Lawson, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 280)
    - Practical Home Tanning and Fur Dressing by Maurice H. Decker, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 281)
    - Hammacher, Schlemmer & Co. "Tools" catalogue No. 630, undated (Box 19, Folder 282)
    - Deep-river Jim's Wilderness Trail Book, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 283)
    - "Hunting, Fishing, and Canoe Trips in Canada" by Canadian National Railways, circa 1933 (Box 19, Folder 284)
    - "The Backgammon Boom" by Walter L. Richard, undated (Box 19, Folder 285)
    - Instructions for RCA Victor Duo 301 record player and catalogue, undated (Box 19, Folder 286)
    - Elements of Music by F. Davenport, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 287)
    - "Four Remarkable Outdoor Books" by The Sporting Gallery and Bookshop, undated (Box 19, Folder 288)
    - Postcard of King George V's funeral, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 289)
    - Program for the Ballets Russes at the Royal Opera House, Covent Garden, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 290)
    - Program for the "Golden Boy" at the Belasco Theatre, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 291)
    - Clippings including New York Times article regarding King George VI's visit to the United States, 1939 June 9, undated (Box 19, Folder 292)
    - Speeches "Broadcast by The Prime Minister Mr. Winston Churchill", 1940-1943 (Box 19, Folder 293)
    - New Republic, 1946 April 15 (Box 19, Folder 294)
    - "Les Restaurants de Paris," Extrait du Guide Gastronomique de la France et International, circa 1946 (Box 19, Folder 295)
- Photographs, 1880-1990s; Series III; 12.84 linear feet (43 boxes)
  The series is organized into four subseries: Formal Portraits of Murphy Family and Immediate Family Members, Formal Portraits of Extended Family and Friends, Snapshots and Candid Portraits, and Photograph Albums. The two Formal Portraits subseries are arranged alphabetically by name of the sitter. Photographs of Sara Murphy as a child and young adult are in Group Portraits: Wiborg Family. The Snapshots and Candid Portraits subseries and Photograph Albums subseries are arranged chronologically.
  The two Formal Portraits subseries are comprised of studio photograph portraits of Gerald and Sara Murphy as well as their children, siblings, parents, extended family members, and friends. Photographs of Gerald and Sara Murphy in their youth, photographed with their families, are grouped with their parents' photographs. Most notably, the first subseries includes Man Ray's portraits of the Murphy family, Sara Murphy's engagement photograph, and a portrait of Gerald Murphy taken using a hinged mirror. A number of photograph studios are represented in the Formal Portraits subseries, including F. M. Somers, E. B. Core, and Marceau and Bellsmith (Cincinnati), Albin Guillot, Lee Miller, A. Sovignity, and Vallois (Paris), and Bachrach, Blackstone Studios, and Pierce (New York). Several of the Murphys' ancestors were prominent military and political figures, such as John Sherman, William Tecumseh Sherman, and Nelson A. Miles, whose portraits are included in the second subseries. The Murphys' friends, including Cole Porter, John Dos Passos, Ada and Archibald MacLeish, and others, are also represented.
  The Snapshots and Candid Portraits and Photograph Albums subseries capture the Murphys, their friends, and extended family at leisure; for example, while traveling, attending parties, skiing, picnicking, sunbathing, and sailing. The Wiborg family was quick to adopt photography and thus Sara Murphy's upbringing is represented in informal photographs, some taken with Kodak No. 2 and Brownie cameras. As adolescents Sara Murphy and her sisters chronicled their activities at "The Dunes" in Easthampton, travels to California, Europe, and India, and created photograph albums that are a window into their lifestyle. Sara Murphy continued to create photograph albums as an adult, most notably capturing the Murphy family's activities from the birth of the children to the death of Patrick Murphy, spanning from roughly 1916 to 1936. A number of the photograph albums are wrapped in tissu de Provence. Over the years various photographs were removed from the albums, and when located, have either been placed back in the album or are accessible in folders accompanying the album.
  Combined, the Snapshots and Candid Portraits and Photograph Albums subseries illuminate the Murphy family's day-to-day life, friendships, and travels. For example, photographs from the "Mad Beach Party" in Antibes in 1923, France, portray the Murphys playing on the beach with Pablo Picasso, Olga Picasso, Count Étienne de Beaumont, Countess Édith de Beaumont, Rue Carpenter, Ginny Carpenter, Gilbert Seldes and others. In 1932 the Murphys sailed their yacht, the Weatherbird, in the Mediterranean with Philip and Ellen Barry and then joined Ernest Hemingway and Pauline Pfeiffer at the L Bar T Ranch in Montana; both trips are represented in the Snapshots and Candid Portraits subseries. The photographs trace the Murphys' various homes and frequent movements, including relocation to Cambridge (Massachusetts), Antibes (France), Montana-Vermala (Switzerland), and Saranac Lake (New York). There are various snapshots showing the Murphys' homes, ranging from Sara Murphy's childhood summer home, "The Dunes," to the Murphys' later homes in Sneden's Landing (Cheer Hall) and East Hampton (Hook Pond and Swan Cove). Together the photographs portray the Murphys' way of life, from friendships to travel, home design, and fashion.
  - Formal Portraits of Murphy and Wiborg Immediate Families
    - Individuals
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy by De Maria Studio, Hempstead, Long Island, circa 1918 (Box 21, Folder 296)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy by W.S. Retch, New York, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 297)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy by Bachrach, 1919-1920 (Box 21, Folder 298)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy in birthday dress, Paris, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 299)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy by Madame Albin Guillot, Paris, circa 1923 (Box 21, Folder 300)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy in pirouette costume, circa 1926 (Box 21, Folder 301)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy in princess costume by A. Dubon (?), circa 1930 (Box 21, Folder 302)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy in evening gown, circa 1935 (Box 21, Folder 303)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy, circa 1940 (Box 21, Folder 304)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy by Studio Harcourt, Paris, circa 1940 (Box 21, Folder 305)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy by Madame Yevonde, London, circa 1940 (Box 21, Folder 306)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy by Blackstone Studios, Shelburne, New York, circa 1940
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy by Blackstone Studios, New York, circa 1940
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy, circa 1980 (Box 21, Folder 307)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy for Condé Naste, circa 1990 (Box 21, Folder 308)
      - Donnelly, Honoria Murphy by Gamblin for Paris Match, circa 1990 (Box 21, Folder 309)
      - Fish, Olga Wiborg by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1890 (Box 21, Folder 310)